SURAJ KUMAR SUBUDHI



CONTACT INFORMATION

- surajkumarsubudhi20@gmail.com
- Bhubaneswar
- +91 7735318452
- Dec 29, 2002
- Indian
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/suraj-ku mar-subudhi-23115a258/

SKILLS

- Data Science
- Java
- Machine Learning
- Python
- Database

LANGUAGES

- English | Advanced
- Hindi | Advanced
- Odia | Advanced
- chinese | Elementary

OBJECTIVE

I love to learn new skills. Ex-Intern at Naval Science & Technological Laboratory - DRDO. I am a C.V. Raman Global University student pursuing BTech in a specialized branch of Artificial Intelligence and Data Science and working on a research project. Technology excites me and I am always in awe of the change it drives in the world. Certain skills that I have worked with include Data Structure and Algorithms (java) , Web Development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and MySQL) , Machine Learning (Python) , and Ubuntu OS. and what I might lack in skills I make up for with my determination to learn. Outside the study life, my passions include being an avid coffee enthusiast and indulging in online gaming.

EXPERIENCE

MACHINE LEARNING INTERN

Naval Science & Technological Laboratory. Visakhapatnam | Dec 2023 - Jan 2024

Worked on Machine Learning an neural Networks with Datasets.

JAVA DEVELOPMENT

Oasis Infobyte. Remote | Jul 2023 - Aug 2023

I have completed internship in Java development, equipping myself with a robust skill set in programming and software development.

DATA SCIENCE FELLOW

Coincent.ai. Remote | Nov 2022 - Jan 2023

I have completed comprehensive training in data science with a focus on utilizing Python. My experience encompasses a range of skills and knowledge, providing me with a solid foundation to tackle real-world data challenges.

WEB DEVELOPMENT INTERN

Bharat Intern. Remote | Jul 2023 - Aug 2023

 Developed responsive and visually appealing web pages using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY-BTECH , COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

C.V. Raman Global University. Bhubaneswar | Sep 2021 - Present

SECONDARY CERTIFICATE PROGRAMS

College of Basic Science and Humanities. Bhubaneswar | Jul 2019 - Mar 2021

SECONDARY CERTIFICATE PROGRAMS

Shree Krishna International School. Bhubaneswar | Apr 2017 - Apr 2019